Every once in a while,
I take it to the internet
and critique people's social
media, look at their websites,
and also just look at their sales process.
Today, we're going to jump straight in.
Just before I begin,
if you wish to have your stuff critiqued,
all you need to do
is click the link in the description.
There's some other stuff beneath that,
but that's all you need for now.
Starting off, Ana Castela,
10K followers already.
Transform bodies, elevate confidence.
I like it.
Online training and nutrition coaching.
This bit here,
sometimes it could be because I'm on
desktop, the whole fact that
we need to populate it,
just double-check that for me.
Sometimes having a more succinct bio
that doesn't need expanding could be good.
Start your transformation,
watch my new video.
One thing I will say
is I'm not sometimes always the biggest
fan of sending people
from Instagram to YouTube.
Think about it this way, right?
When I'm using my phone,
I might be having a poo,
I might be waiting for
a bus.
I might be just doing things where I'm on
Instagram for the sake of being on
Instagram. Sometimes YouTube
is a different mindset.
So for instance,
if I go look at your latest video, okay,
this is a
13-minute video,
so we've got to ask ourselves,
how many people on YouTube are in
the mindset of watching a 13-minute video?
Maybe not that many.
Now,
the issue is they might start watching it.
[dramatic sound] "Oh, no, the bus is here,
got to go," and then YouTube will score
that kind of as an average view duration.
If you want to get people on your YouTube
rather than sending from Instagram, there
are already billions of people on YouTube.
So if I go have a little look at your
channel here, okay, you've been posting
some shorts. Seems a little bit random.
Now,
what if I told you people could find this
video and end up connecting with
your personal brand? The issue here
is this thumbnail is terrible,
I'm afraid. It's awful.
I ate like my worst fitness error for 24
hours. Only oats and water challenge.
Okay, I ate like my worst fitness error.
I don't know what your worst fitness error
is.
For 24 hours, not a very long time,
only oats and water challenge.
So what? Just eating oats and water?
I don't really understand what's
happening.
If I don't understand what's happening,
I'm not really going to watch it.
[dramatic sound] I ate like my worst
fitness error.
No offense, but why would I care
that much about your worst
fitness error? Okay, let's go. Sorry,
no offense, but if you want to
know what's up with your video,
it's the fact that I'm not going to watch
it
because I'm not even critiquing it.
I'm not really interested. Ugh.
Recreates an old,
unhealthy fitness era for a day to
highlight how misguided her
habits once were. Okay, so
if we look at the reason you did it,
your past habits
made you lose muscle, not build it,
trained excessively.
Now she embraces balance, enjoying food,
nourishing her body, and training
intelligently. Hmm. I can't help
but think that maybe
this video should've been
how to fuel correctly for exercise.
Or if we go to your Reels.
Hold on a second.
Hold on a flipping second.
There's two million views.
Two million views on this one.
Two million views, brother.
I was down, but now I'm up, yeah.
It's all God, this ain't no luck, yeah.
I used to be stuck.
Hmm. I'm not quite sure what's happening.
So then again,
there could be a YouTube video here.
Why this glute exercise got me over two
million views.
You could've maybe reused that. Of course,
I picked
someone non-bloody English speaking to
begin with, but
gracias for everything. Okay. Ow.
What I would say is this,
go through here and see what
are your kind of most
compelling Reels, and ask yourself why,
then turn that into a video.
But this, no bueno. No bueno. You're in it
twice. You've just copied your title
and put it in text.
The red, I don't know what that means.
How to fuel,
but even that's a little bit of a boring
video, isn't it?
I would say write down a list of your
perfect client, the struggles they face,
and
make a video that can solve that.
That's what I would say.
That's what I'm saying.
And don't get sucked into memes
or trying to get views for the sake of
it.
These are the ones where you've got to
read the caption.
[singing]
I'm sure you have a lovely personality.
[upbeat music] I'm sure.
Oh,
I can already see you have very
well-developed glutes,
but maybe let's just
talk to camera and try and help people,
or let's move on. Okay.
Jack Cunningham. Filmmaker, marketer,
builder.
Gold Coast, K.
I know your missus won't be happy,
but that could be redundant.
Okay, Demolition Media, Rivalink.
Watch the process.
Of what?
Come with me as I build Demolition Media
as an action sports
videographer.
This I think you could change around.
You could just say,
"I'm an action sports videographer." As I
build Demolition
Media, I don't really understand what
that is, if I'm honest, nor do I care.
Let's have a look. This top-down shot
is a little bit weird.
I'm not going to lie to you. So right now,
you'll notice the camera in front of me
is directly at eye level because I do not
want to seem inferior or superior,
because if you're looking up to me now,
you're in an inferior position, I'm in a
superior position.
You might have some mad monitor in front
of you, I get it, but
it's just a bit weird with a wide lens
looking down.
Time that it takes you.
They're paying for the time
that it saves them.
As a beginner videographer,
it's really easy to underestimate your
value.
And don't get me wrong, in the early days,
just getting in the reps is more
valuable than any money you'll earn.
But as you gain experience,
you'll be able to work more-
I don't really know what this is about.
I get where you're going with it,
but maybe we could've set this up a little
bit
with the first thing
that you would say in it.
You're not charging enough as a
videographer. This is why.
Give me a little bit of a context as to
what's going on. What's going on, brother?
[upbeat music] That's cool.
Yeah, fuck that sh-
[upbeat music] Why do you need
all of this to shoot video
when you can shoot photos with just this?
The short answer is you don't. I use this-
So is this page for your media company,
or is it
to work with new videographers?
B cam on video projects all the time,
and I know heaps of professionals that do
super high-end work.
[dramatic sound] We're back in- Your
perfectionism is killing your progress,
and waiting longer to start is only going
to make things worse.
That's a bit of word salad, bruv. I know,
I get what you're trying to say with a
bit of a sales pitch,
but it's a bit of word salad, bruv.
Been fed up with posting the same content
again and again for months, and I've done
nothing about it because I
was scared of the outcome.
Or more honestly,
that I'd be judged for it.
I was worried that this-
Okay, at this point,
I see you got 61 likes,
and I applaud that, but I just don't
know where this is going
The video would be outside my niche or-
Let's go to the next. And the thing
is here, mate, I'm trying to be as kind as
possible, but even now I'm like, right,
let's just have a look at the next video.
But in the context of people swiping at
home,
that's going to someone else's video.
Sunday essentials.
I'm just a bit confused on what you
do or who you are
Do you want bookings as a videographer,
or do you want to work with other people?
Let's have a look here. Demolition Media,
photography, videography. Okay, cool.
Right, yeah. Rival Link.
I don't even know what this is, mate.
I'm a bit confused.
Some of your content here
is kind of leaning into a bit of the
B2B space,
and you just don't really allude to that.
So the first thing I'm going to say
is when I get here,
I'm just a bit confused.
"Come with me as I build Demolition
Media." Who are you talking to?
Because here,
"Is this the ultimate vlog combo?" Then
here, "Every beginner..."
I'm a bit lost, mate.
I want to know what you do
or what you're trying to do.
And even here, mate,
I come to your website.
This all looks good,
but I don't know what you do.
I don't know what I'm here for.
I'm just watching dudes on bikes,
and I come down. "The Vision.
Driven by a passion for action." I'm like,
still don't know what you do.
Cool, there's some brands here. Who am I?
Don't care. Why am I here?
What is the sole purpose?
If I show you this,
let's go one of my squeeze pages,
30 Days in 30 Ways.
There'll be links to all of these in the
description. It's pretty straightforward.
30 days,
30 insights on ways to optimize your
business. That's what it is.
Then if we go to Lead... Actually,
the easiest
way for me is going to do this.
Every single page
that you're going to go to that's
one of my websites
is very clearly going to show you exactly
what it is.
So we've got the outcome,
become a master in short-form content
creation.
We've got a bespoke BSL.
We've got pricing.
So we call this above the fold in
marketing.
So everything you land on in this page
is above the fold.
This is the really,
really important stuff here.
Like yours was just the video, which is...
No, it's not fine.
There's no function to it. Then,
let's say you want to have a look at an
email
marketing course that I've got here.
Everyone talks about your first 10 grand a
month.
Wait till you have your first 10 grand
email. You think, "Oh, that'd be good.
Cool.
Find out more." Want to master your email
marketing.
Let's go personal trainer.
I have an offer for personal trainers
here.
Finally, a course
that answers the question,
how the fuck do I run a better PT
business? Only people
that want to run a better PT business
are going to get
interest at this point.
So every page has to very clearly let
people know what it is
that they're going to get.
Let's have a look here.
The only sales page template you'll ever
need.
All of these things I put in there so
that when you land on a website, you know
exactly what you're getting,
what it costs, whether or not it's free,
what you're
getting.
I just feel a bit confused by your stuff,
brother. Right. All right.
Let's try this geezer.
Let's try this geezer. Okay.
My man. Oh, by the way,
the glasses can probably come off.
The thing is,
I put them on because basically it just
makes the thumbnail easier to
click. If I look at my statistics,
when I wear these in the thumb,
you get more
clicks.
And then if I wasn't wearing them in the
video, you'd be like, "What?
What's going on, brother?"
Okay,
top porn addiction recovery coach for men.
All right, 2,000 posts, 7,000 followers.
I would say that's an indication
that maybe we're not quite tapping into
everything that we need from the content,
but let's get into it, brother.
Let's get into it.
You're edging for hours, and this
is why it can be so devastating on your
time
and ener-
I feel like I've just landed in someone
else's conversation.
I'm probably going to leave.
One book sparked this guy's recovery from
porn. Okay.
One of the things that
is so devious about porn addiction as
opposed to other addictions
is how many of these consequences are so
subtle and so hard to see because they
build up over time.
And it's-
Okay, I don't mind you clipping pods.
I don't mind,
but it's never going to be as effective as
actually [grunts] getting
content. [grunts] Porn is making you soft.
Porn is ruining your life.
Porn is killing you.
That's what I want to hear.
What happens if I continue living my life
this way?
You will keep fading, not in a cinematic,
tragic way, but in a
quiet, pathetic one. Every-
Hmm. Maybe a bit too dramatic
... who you are today, what y-
Maybe a bit too dramatic for me.
Bit too dramatic for me.
If you can live a life where the default,
just the first thought that pops into
your head is-
I'm not sure if I'm mad on this music
... your attitude towards recovery
is going to be this-
The hooks, we need a bit of work.
I need you to really bring the
hook to the forefront. Tell me a fact.
Porn is ruining your relationship.
Let me explain.
If you want to help people,
the person that I would think
about has to be old Dr. Julie. She is
fantastic. She's a bit of a fox as well.
Don't care. Who knows? I'm saying Dr.
Julie, if you're out there,
I think you're a fox.
Now-
Don't make this mistake
... hook, don't make this mistake.
What mistake?
She's pointing at a fish tank.
Curiosity is built. Let's get into it.
You're working on your own happiness.
Working on your own happiness.
Who isn't working on their own happiness?
The current pool size for this video
is fucking nine billion people.
Imagine this is you, and this-
Set up. Imagine this is you, and this
is your life
... is your life.
Now we're trying to imagine how our life
could be a fish in a fish tank, and do you
know what?
The only way we're going to find out
is to keep listening to this set up
till we get a payoff.
But like most people's lives, there
are problems that can make it
toxic. If a-
Oh, a visual for it being toxic. Come on
... fish is living in a toxic environment,
eventually it gets
sick,
so you take her out of the dirty water
and put her in a new
tank for a while. Can-
Great transition
... how you take a break,
you go on holiday for a few weeks into a
new
environment, and it helps.
Everything gets better and feels great
for a while, until you return
and go right back to
that toxic situation again.
And it doesn't matter how clean the
water was on your break
or how refreshed you feel.
Eventually,
you will get sick again.
If you want to thrive in the long term,
you have to focus on cleaning up the
environment that is affecting you every
day.
I'm a psychologist. Follow for more.
Oh.
See, look, it's a soft call to action,
a call to action to follow for more, and
usually I don't like people asking for a
follow, but that is just exquisite.
This is what we need to do.
We need to have a visual.
We need to Think of a hook.
We need to have a setup.
We need to have a payoff.
We need to really strategize that content,
brother.
And this just seems to me like a...
Do you know what?
I'd say it's probably harder the way
you're doing it with these kind of clips.
And again, you notice I try
and take my headphones out
when I'm talking because
it's personal, right?
It doesn't matter how-
If
this is from a podcast, fine, but
if you're doing a piece to camera,
why you got
headphones in? Why? These just aren't
really performing well enough for me,
brother.
And you're a little bit too close,
the music's a bit dramatic,
there's no setups,
there's no payoffs. And also,
do you know what?
I could be completely wrong.
I might need you to not dramaticize porn
quite so...
For me,
surely porn addiction sits on a spectrum.
There must be a cohort of happy wankers.
You know what I mean?
There must be happy,
happy wankers who can have the odd little
bash of the
bishop, and they're fine.
But not everyone is going to die
if they wank.
You know what I mean?
That's what I'm trying to say.
A global movement towards freedom.
Look, let's just say, for some people,
their wanky wanky
is probably not congruent with a good
and happy life, and they're the people we
need to help. You know what I mean,
brother? You know what I mean.
Too many things here. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
I land here, I'm like,
"Get me out of here." Okay,
we've got the Breaking Porn
Addiction podcast, unhook stabbers,
free discovery call.
There's just a lot going on here. Okay,
YouTube looks good, pretty good
If you can master these three key steps,
your struggles with porn addiction-
All right,
let's have a look at your number one.
Number one. Okay.
You see how all your latest videos look
like this? They look all right.
If I go to your most popular,
they look nothing like that.
So you see this one,
"If I started my porn recovery journey in
2025,
I'd do this." Let's do that video again.
Let's do this video again. Why?
Because it fucking worked.
"How I avoid the binge after a relapse
with porn." Hmm?
I'm not sure the thumbnail's fully nailed
here. You've got two photos.
I'm not really seeing the before
and the after.
"Should you stop masturbating?" These do
need a bit of work, I must say.
But copy this one, because,
for whatever reason, this one did well.
And then I think that you should have...
You wanted to book a discovery call,
right?
If you can master-
Yeah, cool. This is fine. This is fine.
Call to action's there.
It's just a difficult one, isn't it?
I would say I can't connect with that.
If you had videos on how to wank less,
I might be more inclined to watch.
But you know what?
Sometimes you're traveling,
you're all jet-lagged, you're in a
new time zone, you're staying in a hotel.
No one's awake yet.
It's 4:00 in the morning,
and there's just nothing better than a
little tommy tank.
You know what I mean? I know
that it could ruin a lot of people's
lives, but
there's a lot of high-functioning wankers
out there. Ask my manager.
He doesn't even masturbate,
he's just a wanker.
[laughs] Let's do a couple more. Right.
Deep Health Training, Manny Diaz.
Let's look into it.
Kettlebell instructor.
Never vibed with kettlebells,
not gonna lie.
NGL. Okay.
"Bridging the gap for a living longer
and better
with kettlebells." Hmm.
Bridging the what gap? Living longer
and better.
Longer, better.
I don't really understand that. Founder.
Now, again, bro,
I'm at the Huntington Beach Kettlebell
Club. Okay, cool.
I like that. Founder?
Bruh.
You started a kettlebell business
that you do on the beach, right?
You're not floating on the footsie, bro.
I want you to do well, brother.
I really want you to do well. But founder,
I
know you're American, bro,
but let's not say...
I got told to put founder in my LinkedIn
bio, but we got, like, a $20 million
FMCG business, and even I thought it
was cringe.
So let's just say, "Come on, man." Okay.
No link in the description.
No call to action. Let's get into it.
This year,
I'm leaning into a lot of discomfort.
Hmm. Look, bro, I'm a throw it out there.
First of all, hashtags don't do anything.
You're in good shape in both of them,
right?
And it wasn't kettlebells that did this.
You must have restricted calories,
you increased energy output.
It wasn't the kettlebells that did this.
Today we're gonna make one of my favorite
recipes, and that is salmon
over farro.
This will literally do nothing for your
knees unless
you have a plan.
Part of having healthy knees
is your ability...
Just because it burns doesn't mean it's
doing anything for your...
Just because you ignore knee pain doesn't
mean it's gonna go away
All of this content seems to be about knee
pain.
I thought it was about kettlebells.
[singing] Just call me the man I need.
Tell me you've got something to give.
Hold on a second.
Let's start this one again.
[singing] The man I need.
This is a bit of an unnecessary setup.
Horizontal row, kettlebell.
You lengthen the muscle. I suppose
if you're trying to promote people.
[singing] Something to give. I want it.
I kinda like it when you call me sugar.
Do you know what my gripe
is with kettlebell workouts, bro? Right.
It's just an easy to hold onto weight.
That's it.
It's just an easy weight to hold onto.
That is it. That's it. And yet,
convenient.
And all of this content, to me,
should be around convenience.
It should be around how
if you just want to take up one square
meter
in your house and have all your gym
equipment in there, it's kettlebells.
Because the truth is,
if you've got more room
and the ability to do more, you're
gonna get a sweat rack
and you're probably gonna get better
results, right?
I would also be clipping the hell out of
Rogan and all the good things he has to
say about kettlebells and making
that part of my identity.
But the fact I've watched loads of your
stuff and just found out about knee pain,
you're not directing me anywhere.
In your application,
you did actually give me a website,
so let's have a look at
that. Deep Health. What is Deep Health?
No one in the form of health has ever
said, "I would love it deep." "Oh, what
can I do for your health,
sir?" "Get it deeper." I don't understand
the
brand. Manny Diaz, Deep Health.
Deep Health? Okay.
Remember we spoke about above the fold
before? I land here.
"Build a framework through Deep Health
that elevates your training potential,
nutrition, behaviors,
restoration." You don't even mention
kettlebells.
So that does nothing for me.
That looks good, does nothing for me.
We've got links to socials
which take me the wrong way.
"Don't let bad health get in the way of
living your best life." Bad health?
I thought you were the kettlebell guy.
Look, this needs a bit of work, mate.
I'll be honest with you.
I don't really know who you are
or what you do.
I feel like we need to get
that across a little bit better.
If you have a kettlebell club
and you're putting kettlebell instructor
here, surely
everything just has to be kettlebells.
You sell kettlebell workouts,
you make kettlebell content,
you do kettlebell
tutorials. The thing is here,
I think you're trying to be a specialist
in too many
things.
It makes it incredibly difficult for me to
keep up, I must say. I must say.
All right. I hope you found those useful.
Links are in the description.
Get stuck into them.